{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Which of the following data constraints would be used to specify that the value of cells in a column must be one of a specific set of possible values?", "opta": "A domain constraint", "optb": "A range constraint", "optc": "An intrarelation constraint", "optd": "An interrelation constraint", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In a 1:N relationship, the foreign key is placed in:", "opta": "either table without specifying parent and child tables.", "optb": "the parent table.", "optc": "the child table.", "optd": "either the parent table or the child table.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following column properties specifies whether or not cells in a column must contain a data value?", "opta": "Null status", "optb": "Data type", "optc": "Default value", "optd": "Data constraints", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A primary key should be defined as:", "opta": "NULL.", "optb": "NOT NULL.", "optc": "Either of the above can be used.", "optd": "None of the above are correct.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following column properties would be used to specify that cells in a column must contain a monetary value?", "opta": "Null status", "optb": "Data type", "optc": "Default value", "optd": "Data constraints", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following situation requires the use of ID-dependent entities?", "opta": "Association relationships only", "optb": "Multivalued attributes only", "optc": "Archetype/instance relationships only", "optd": "All of the above use ID dependent entities", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A foreign key is:", "opta": "a column containing the primary key of another table.", "optb": "used to define data types.", "optc": "used to define null status.", "optd": "all of the above are above correct.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following columns is(are) are required in a table?", "opta": "A foreign key", "optb": "An alternate key", "optc": "A primary key", "optd": "A surrogate key.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In a 1:1 relationship, the foreign key is placed in:", "opta": "either table without specifying parent and child tables.", "optb": "the parent table.", "optc": "the child table.", "optd": "either the parent table or the child table.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following column properties would be used to specify that cells in a column must be immediately filled with a monetary value of $10,000?", "opta": "Null status", "optb": "Data type", "optc": "Default value", "optd": "Data constraints", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The identifier of an entity will become the ________ of the new table.", "opta": "foreign key", "optb": "main attribute", "optc": "primary key", "optd": "identity key", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following data constraints would be used to specify that the value of a cell in one column must be less than the value of a cell in another column in the same row of the same table?", "opta": "A domain constraint", "optb": "A range constraint", "optc": "An intrarelation constraint", "optd": "An interrelation constraint", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A unique, DBMS-supplied identifier used as the primary key of a relation is called a(n):", "opta": "primary key.", "optb": "foreign key.", "optc": "composite key.", "optd": "surrogate key.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is not true about surrogate keys?", "opta": "They are short.", "optb": "They are fixed.", "optc": "They have meaning to the user.", "optd": "They are numeric.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "For every relationship, how many possible types of actions are there when enforcing minimum cardinalities?", "opta": "Two", "optb": "Three", "optc": "Four", "optd": "Six", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which constraint requires that the binary relationship indicate all combinations that must appear in the ternary relationship?", "opta": "MUST COVER", "optb": "MUST NOT", "optc": "Both of the above.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Each entity is represented as a(n):", "opta": "tuple.", "optb": "table.", "optc": "attribute.", "optd": "file.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "For every relationship, how many possible sets of minimum cardinalities are there?", "opta": "Two", "optb": "Three", "optc": "Four", "optd": "Six", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If a relationship has a cascade updates constraint, then if ________ in the parent table is changed, then the same change will automatically be made to any corresponding foreign key value.", "opta": "the primary key", "optb": "any alternate key", "optc": "a surrogate key", "optd": "a foreign key", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following column properties would be used to specify that cells in a column must contain a monetary value that is less than another monetary value in the same row?", "opta": "Null status", "optb": "Data type", "optc": "Default value", "optd": "Data constraints", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}